Imagine falling asleep nestled by nature.
Our Fair Trade farmers in the forests of Sri Lanka
gently tap into the sustainable rubbitries
collecting pure latex sap.
Every drop supports not only your comfort
but also a thriving fair trade community
that we are proud to stand behind.
The rubbitry sap takes a short trip from the forests
to our factory in Colombo.
Our full sap is purified, especially at a small amount
of binding ingredients and whip it into a frothy fluffy foam.
The foam is steamed baked at 212 degrees.
Think of it as the world's most comfy cake.
After rigorous quality controls,
the foam blocks are then shaped to Illinois
to become your new mattress.
In our Chicago factory, every detail matters.
Our 12 dedicated sewers place thousands of
overlocking stitches, one by one.
Even on seams you'll never see.
Once the meticulous sewing is complete,
our warehouse steam takes over.
The covers are quilted and assembled into each mattress.
Then they are tested for comfort, durability and safety
and then shipped to their new home.